Sir.
Please wait a moment.
The report will be ready shortly.
Damn it.
We fell for a diversionary tactic.
Hurry back to the hospital.
The lab report might've been stolen.
Wait for me!
Doctor!
Where's the doctor?
Dr. Lu was drugged.
They're treating him right now.
What?
What about Mr. Li's toxicology report?
Why is it missing?
I remember he wrote it.
And the bracelet, it was tested too.
Bracelet?
What bracelet?
Dr. Lu said
he needed to test everything on the victim
to pinpoint the source of the poison.
Mr. Li was wearing a beaded bracelet.
It was sent for testing too.
This is the bag for the bracelet.
Aconitine.
On this bracelet...
there is highly toxic aconitine.
The bracelet...
Wear it, it'll keep you safe.
I remember now.
It belongs to that old witch.
I shouldn't have let that old witch go.
Let's go to the Spirit Medium's house.
Okay.
I was ordered by Mr. Li
to kidnap Old Ding's grandson, Xiaobao,
and drown him as a human foundation sacrifice.
These past few days,
I've been having nightmares every day.
I dreamt of Xiaobao coming for me.
He said
he wants me to pay with my life.
You took a life.
The burden of your sins is too heavy.
You're haunted by Xiaobao's evil spirit.
Then what should I do?
How can I drive the evil spirit away?
Spirit Medium,
please help me.
I'll perform Spirit Summoning with Rice.
I will invite Xiaobao's soul into my body.
You will apologize to him personally,
and beg for his forgiveness.
If Xiaobao forgives you,
he won't haunt you anymore.
Okay.
I'll do as you say.
I will apologize to Xiaobao.
Spirit Summoning with Rice is perilous.
It trades a soul for a soul.
Therefore,
while I am casting the spell,
the candles in this room
must not go out.
The candle flame is the Soul-Guiding Lamp.
If the lamp goes out
while Xiaobao's soul
is possessing my body,
his soul can't return to the underworld,
and my soul won't be able to come back.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I will definitely protect the candles
so the Soul-Guiding Lamp doesn't go out.
There is a path to heaven,
and a door to the underworld.
White rice paves the way to the netherworld.
Where is the soul of Ding Xiaobao?
With white rice as the medium
and the spirit lamp as the guide,
Ding Xiaobao,
Three Ethereal Souls and Seven Mortal Forms, possess me!
Come! Come!
Come!
Spirit Medium?
What's wrong, Spirit Medium?
This candle absolutely cannot go out!
Otherwise, the dead soul can't go back!
Don't move.
You she-devil!
You really are a reincarnated Rakshasa.
Death follows you wherever you go.
This is too freaky!
An evil spirit really is claiming lives!
This smell...
Was it you?
Come back to the police station with me.
No.
Don't touch him!
His hands are poisoned!
What poison?
Aconitine.
The newspaper had this smell too.
The killer
used ink containing aconitine
to print on the newspaper.
Aconitine is extremely toxic.
A single drop is fatal.
The Spirit Medium got poison on her hands.
Her finger was cut,
and the poison entered her bloodstream,
causing her death.
I understand.
Go wash the poison off and change.
Okay, I'll go wash right now.
You go back to the police station first
and take the body with you.
I'll investigate further.
All right.
What's wrong?
Bro Xun is allergic to cat hair.
It seems this room
used to have a cat.
Look.
I was right, wasn't I?
A cat.
The night Mengzhu died,
a cat also appeared in the Li Manor.
The miss was bitten by a cat as a child,
and was terrified of them.
The Master forbade keeping cats in the manor.
But that day,
the Spirit Medium brought a cat inside.
Father,
I want to swap rooms with you.
So that means
the Spirit Medium purposely brought the cat.
Her goal was
to scare her with the cat at night.
Mengzhu was afraid of cats,
so she swapped rooms with Mr. Li.
As a result,
she became the scapegoat in the puppet murder.
And who is this man
in the photo with the Spirit Medium?
Look.
And this All-In-One Restorative Pill.
I've seen this bottle before.
That day, the Spirit Medium came to see the Master.
Master.
This is the All-In-One Restorative Pill I made.
It wards off evil and restores vitality.
Hurry and take it.
Hurry up and take it.
After taking the Spirit Medium's pill,
the Master suffered from internal heat,
and got blisters all over his mouth.
Right.
Chunmei and her brother
wanted to poison Master Li with tea.
But the Spirit Medium
used the All-In-One Restorative Pill early
to give Master Li mouth ulcers,
so he couldn't drink hot tea,
thus escaping disaster.
Master,
this Spirit Medium really has some skills.
She can even predict the future.
Later,
the day the chandelier crushed Second Madam,
they'd agreed to try on suits at the firm.
I have a big deal.
I can only discuss it with you.
Master, this is bad!
The Second Madam is dead!
What?
The mysterious big client
went to buy the book from Mr. Li,
which delayed his return home,
saving him for the third time.
Right.
When Third Madam was by the well,
the night she was poisoned singing opera,
where was Mr. Li?
The Master went to the Spirit Medium's house.
Master Li,
I see a dark aura on your forehead.
I fear you will face a bloody disaster soon.
Why isn't the Master back yet?
I agreed with him
that after singing Cinnabar Well,
we would go to Cuixiang Restaurant for dinner.
Spirit Medium,
I made plans with my wife.
I'm going to hear her sing opera.
I should go back first.
Let's talk another day.
You absolutely cannot leave.
I'll perform an exorcism ritual for you now.
Spirits of heaven and earth,
Taishang Laojun, teach me to slay demons!
Madam, what's wrong?
Somebody!
Somebody, help!
What demon dare not submit?
What ghost dare stand in my way?
So,
the expert behind Mr. Li
is the Spirit Medium.
Then tell me, why did the Spirit Medium
want to help Mr. Li?
It was for your family heirloom, of course.
Mr. Li hid the book.
If he died,
the book would never be found.
Jiang Huai,
that book of yours,
what exactly is written in it?
Heavenly Craftsmanship
records hundreds of ancient crafting methods.
There are many wicked people in the world
who are desperate to get it.
So you're saying,
to get the book, the Spirit Medium
painstakingly set up this trap.
But she was afraid of being exposed,
so she poisoned Mr. Li.
If the Spirit Medium wanted to poison Mr. Li,
then why did she
also poison herself?
True.
But here at the Spirit Medium's place,
we didn't see Heavenly Craftsmanship either.
Which means she didn't get the book.
Master,
look at this bowl.
Is there anything special about it?
This bowl
dates back to the Yanbei warlord era.
What's the Spirit Medium's real background?
The Spirit Medium fled here from Yanbei.
There are few outsiders in Li Town.
As for those in town with a Yanbei accent,
there is one other person.
He's from her hometown.
From her hometown?
Who is it?
It's...